A Guide to the Papers of Alexander H. H. Stuart and the related Stuart and Baldwin families
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- SERIES III: CORRESPONDENCE OF ALEXANDER H.H. STUART
  - John S. Gallaher, 1851-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - Robert H. Gallaher, 1851-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - Alexander Galt, 1851 Jul 31 (Box Box 3)
  - J. Garland, 1853 Feb 2 (Box Box 3)
  - William H. Garland, 1850, 1852 (Box Box 3)
  - William Garnett, 1851-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - George Washington's Birthday Celebration Committee, Rome, Georgia, 868 Feb 11 (Box Box 3)
  - R.T. Gibson, 1851-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - W.M. Gilliam, 1852 Mar 15 (Box Box 3)
  - T.H. Gilmer, 1850 Sep 27 (Box Box 3)
  - Thomas W. Gilmer, 1843 Dec 13 (Box Box 3)
  - W.W. Gilmer, 1841 Apr 15 (Box Box 3)
  - William I. Goggin, 1850, 1852 (Box Box 3)
  - G. Goldenberg, 1849 Feb 2 (Box Box 3)
  - J.T. Gordon, 1852 Jul 9 (Box Box 3)
  - W.A. Gorman, 1852 Dec 14 (Box Box 3)
  - J. Thompson Graham, 1852 Oct 24 (Box Box 3)
  - William A. Graham, 1850-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - Horace Greeley, 1852 Jan 25 (Box Box 3)
  - F. Gremger, 1851 Sep 3 (Box Box 3)
  - William Grever, 1850 Oct 3 (Box Box 3)
  - Benjamin Edwards Grey, 1852 Mar 17 (Box Box 3)
  - George G. Grove, 1851 Oct 12 (Box Box 3)
  - Francis Grund, 1851 (Box Box 3)
  - Hiland Hall, 1851 Sep 20 (Box Box 3)
  - Nathan Kelsey Hall, 1853, 1871 (Box Box 3)
  - J.K Hanson, 1852 Apr 3 (Box Box 3)
  - J. Hardesty, 1848 Oct 25 (Box Box 3)
  - Kenton Harper, 1847, 1850-1851 (Box Box 3)
  - J. Morrison Harris, 1850 May 20 (Box Box 3)
  - Judge N. Harrison, 18[?] Sep 3 (Box Box 3)
  - Solomon George Haven, 1857 Oct 8 (Box Box 3)
  - A.M. Hay, 1852 Aug 25 (Box Box 3)
  - T.S. Haymond, 1851 Dec 20 (Box Box 3)
  - Isaac Hazlehurst, 1857 Jun 24 (Box Box 3)
  - Richard H. Henderson, Virginia Colonization Society, 1837 Oct 28 (Box Box 3)
  - Professor Joseph Henry, 1852 Aug 4 (Box Box 3)
  - Britton A. Hill, 1852 Feb 6 & 9 (Box Box 3)
  - William L. Hodge, 1852 Jan 20 (Box Box 3)
  - J.E. Holmes, 1851 Oct 25 (Box Box 3)
  - Rev. Samuel R. Houston, 1852 Feb 24 (Box Box 3)
  - M.U. Houston, 1850 (Box Box 3)
  - Benjamin C. Howard, 1852 Jul 30 (Box Box 3)
  - Robert Hull, 1851 Oct 3 (Box Box 3)
  - Andrew Hunter, 1851 Nov 27 & Dec 9 (Box Box 3)
  - R.M.T. Hunter, 1852 Feb 3 (Box Box 3)
  - John Daniel Imboden, 1850-1853 (Box Box 3)
  - J.K Irving, 1851-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - G.W. Israel to Alexander H.H. Stuart through President Millard Fillmore, 1853 Feb 8 (Box Box 3)
  - S.D. Jacobs, 1851 Nov 13 (Box Box 3)
  - John Janney, 1866-1867 (Box Box 3)
  - G.N. Johnson, 1840 May 14 (Box Box 3)
  - R. Johnson, 1850-1853 (Box Box 3)
  - William B. Kayser, 1852 Sep 22 (Box Box 3)
  - John P. Kennedy, 1850-1854 (Box Box 3)
  - Joseph C.G. Kennedy, [1847]-1870 (Box Box 3)
  - Kent Lumber Company, 1852 Oct 27 (Box Box 3)
  - Andrew W. Kercheval, 1867 Feb 14 (Box Box 3)
  - William Kerr, 1851 Nov 14 (Box Box 3)
  - [Samuel] D. King, 1851 Jul 14 (Box Box 3)
  - Jeffers Kinney, 1852 (Box Box 3)
  - Nicholas Kinney, 1841 & 1851 (Box Box 3)
  - R.H. Kinney, 1841 Jun 25 (Box Box 3)
  - William Kinney, 1841-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - O.B. Knode, 1852 Jan 22 (Box Box 3)
  - F.A. Kownslar, 1833 Jun 24 (Box Box 3)
  - Daniel Kraber, 1831 (Box Box 3)
  - J.D. Kurtz, 1853 Jan 17 (Box Box 3)
  - John H.B. Latrobe, 1838 Sep 1 (Box Box 3)
  - Joseph S. Leake, 1831 Nov 3 (Box Box 3)
  - Adam Lee, 1831 Mar 11 (Box Box 3)
  - John Letcher, 1856 May 2 (Box Box 3)
  - [Will H. Lewis ?], n.d. (Box Box 3)
  - John Tayloe Lomax, 1842 Jul 8 (Box Box 3)
  - L. Luckett, 1859-1861 (Box Box 3)
  - James Lyons, 1841 Aug 20 (Box Box 3)
  - Joseph S. Machie, 1851-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - James McDonald, 1851 Oct 8 (Box Box 3)
  - Redick McKee, 1851-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - Thomas M.S. McKennan, 1851 Oct 29 (Box Box 3)
  - Louis McKenzie, 1860 Aug 31 (Box Box 3)
  - William McLaughlin, 1857 Nov 23 (Box Box 3)
  - Theodorick B. McRobert, 1850-1851 (Box Box 3)
  - F. Madera, 1851 Dec 30 (Box Box 3)
  - Allan B. & John T. Magruder, 1851-1853 (Box Box 3)
  - James Maguire, 1851 Mar 29 (Box Box 3)
  - Francis Mallory, 1851-1852 (Box Box 3)
  - N. Marmion to Messrs. Baldwin & Stuart, Attorneys-at-Law, 1834 (Box Box 3)
  - Timothy Marmion, n.y. Dec 21 (Box Box 3)
  - J.K. Marshall, 1852 Jan 30 (Box Box 3)
  - Thomas A. Marshall, 1833 (Box Box 3)
  - Thomas Martin, 1830 Jul 27 (Box Box 3)
  - William Martin, 1867 Jan 16 & Feb 10 (Box Box 3)
  - Maryland Institute, Officers & Managers, 1851 Oct 6 (Box Box 3)
  - James Murray Mason, 1853 Oct 22 (Box Box 4)
  - [John Young] Mason, 1851 Dec 30 (Box Box 4)
  - James W. Massie, 1871 Apr 17 (Box Box 4)
  - Thomas E. Massie, 1852 May 5 (Box Box 4)
  - Joel E. Mathews, 1851-1852 (Box Box 4)
  - Tyre Maupin, 1848, 1852 (Box Box 4)
  - R. Mayo, 1852 (Box Box 4)
  - Thompson G. Martin, 1831, 1834 (Box Box 4)
  - Members of the Virginia Legislature to the President and Members of the Cabinet (Box Box 4)
  - Memoranda of Alexander H.H. Stuart while Secretary of the Interior (Box Box 4)
  - C.F. Mercer, 832 May 28 (Box Box 4)
  - Hugh Mercer, 1851 Jul 4 & Feb 22 (Box Box 4)
  - [S.] C.M. Merillat, 1852 Jun 1 (Box Box 4)
  - C.H. Merritt, 1851 Sep 30, Oct 20 (Box Box 4)
  - Thomas J. Michie, 1845-1852 (Box Box 4)
  - William C. Micou, 1852 Oct 20 (Box Box 4)
  - Daniel F. Miller to Thomas Corwin, 1852 Aug 17 (Box Box 4)
  - Jacob Welsh Miller, 1852 May 5 (Box Box 4)
  - James Miller, 1852 Dec 1 (Box Box 4)
  - Zophar Mills, 1851 Jul 8 (Box Box 4)
  - Joseph L. Mitchell, 1852 Feb 7 (Box Box 4)
  - John Moebus, 1852 Jun 22 (Box Box 4)
  - John Moffett, 1852 Jun 27 (Box Box 4)
  - Thomas S. Moffett, 1834 Jan 27 (Box Box 4)
  - Henry W. Moncure, 1852 Jun 9 (Box Box 4)
  - Charles P. Montague, 1852 Jun 8 (Box Box 4)
  - D.E. Moore, 1831 & 1841 (Box Box 4)
  - John K. Moore, 1850 & 1852 (Box Box 4)
  - L.T. Moore, 1851 Oct 10, 18, 21 (Box box 4)
  - Samuel M.D. Moore, 1830-1852 (Box Box 4)
  - John Moorman, 1852 Mar 4 (Box Box 4)
  - [W.?] Morris, 1852 Dec 1 (Box Box 4)
  - C.L. Mosby, 1831 & 1851 (Box Box 4)
  - [Alexander] Moseley, 1841-1852 (Box Box 4)
  - J.W. Myers, 1851 Dec 11 (Box Box 4)
  - Thomas Nairu, 1850 Oct 23 (Box Box 4)
  - C.W. Newton, 1851-1852 (Box Box 4)
  - Isaac C. Newton, 1853 Jan 15 (Box Box 4)
  - Dr. C.N. Nichols, 1852 Nov 23 (Box Box 4)
  - William Ogden Niles, 1850 Nov 12 (Box Box 4)
  - John A. North, 1852 Aug 14 (Box Box 4)
  - John A. [Parker?], 1873 Oct 27 (Box Box 4)
  - William Elisha Peters, 1876 Nov 23 (Box Box 4)
  - F. Petrie, 1878 Aug 12 (Box Box 4)
  - Eb Phlegar, 1841 Apr 24 (Box Box 4)
  - L.M. Powell, 1860 Oct (Box Box 4)
  - W.A. Powell, 1868 Dec 16 (Box Box 4)
  - William Ballard Preston, 1848 Jun 15 (Box Box 4)
  - Charles Radziminski, 1852 Aug 1 (Box Box 4)
  - Robert Ridgway, 1859 Jan 9 (Box Box 4)
  - Lawrence Riggs, 1850-1851 (Box Box 4)
  - Alexander Rives, 860-1861 (Box Box 4)
  - William Cabell Rives, 1859 & 1868 (Box Box 4)
  - William Barton Rogers, 1881 Jul 7 (Box Box 4)
  - W.H. Ruffner, 1851 Dec 5 (Box Box 4)
  - Benjamin Rush, 1874 Aug 4 (Box Box 4)
  - John C. Rusmisell, 1851 Dec 25 (Box Box 4)
  - N. Sargeant, 1858-1859 (Box Box 4)
  - R.E. Scott, 1852 May 22 (Box Box 4)
  - Joseph Segar, 1852 Mar 11 (Box Box 4)
  - Hugh W. Sheffey, 1848-1852 (Box Box 4)
  - W.G. [Snethen ?], 1852 Oct 9 (Box Box 4)
  - Lord Stirling, 1852 Sep 11 (Box Box 4)
  - Samuel Strong, 1851 Nov 5 (Box Box 4)
  - James French Strother, 1852 Jun 8 (Box Box 4)
  - Alexander H.H. Stuart Letters, 1837-1873 (Box Box 4)
  - Archibald P. Stuart, 1850 Sep 29 (Box Box 4)
  - Eleanor Briscoe Stuart, n.d. (Box Box 4)
  - J.E.B. Stuart, 1851 & 1857 (Box Box 4)
  - Oscar J.C. Stuart, 1859 Aug 8 (Box Box 4)
  - Isaac H. Sturgeon, 1852 Feb 4 (Box Box 4)
  - G.W. Summers, 1844 Feb 28, May 30 (Box Box 4)
  - William T. Sutherlin, 1870, 1873 (Box Box 4)
  - [J.H. Tagart?], 1852 Nov 28 (Box Box 4)
  - William H. Terrill, 1871 Nov 17 (Box Box 4)
  - Lucas P. Thompson, 1855 Jan 21 (Box Box 4)
  - Nicholas K. Trout, 1867 Jan 20 (Box Box 4)
  - Unidentified Letters to Alexander H.H. Stuart, 1839-[1861?] (Box Box 4)
  - Upshur County Citizens, 1859 Apr 6 (Box Box 4)
  - Thomas Walter, 1851 Nov 6 (Box Box 4)
  - Washington College Literary Society, 1857 Apr 28 (Box Box 4)
  - John Watt, 1861 Dec 3 (Box Box 4)
  - Daniel Webster, 1842-1851 (Box Box 4)
  - William J. Willey, 1861 May 7 (Box Box 4)
  - Robert Winthrop, 1851, 1882-1889 (Box Box 4)
  - Henry A. Wise, 1869 Feb 3, 5, 8 (Box Box 4)
  - R.N. Wood, 1856 Apr 13 (Box Box 4)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Engraving of Alexander H.H. Stuart by J.C. Buttre
  - Land Grant to Thomas Turk signed by Beverley Randolph, 1789 Aug 31
  - Land Grant to [Monticu ?] Allen signed by Robert Brooke, 1796 Mar 30
  - 9 Land Grants to Archibald Stuart, agent of the Greenbrier Company, signed by James Monroe, 1800 May 12-15
  - Land Grant to Joseph Boyers signed by John Floyd, 1830 Sep 1
- MICROFILM
  Positive copies of microfilms produced by The Library of Virginia
  - Archibald Stuart Papers, 1768-1831, n.d.; (75 items) (Reel M-260 REEL 1)
  - Alexander H.H. Stuart Correspondence, 1830-1844; (40 items) (Reel M-260 (continued)REEL 2)
  - Alexander H.H. Stuart Papers, 1845-1850; (15 items) (Reel M-261 REEL 3)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, Deeds, Grants, etc. of the Stuart Family, 1770-1896, n.d.; (45 items) (Reel M-262 REEL 4)